<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayoub Gharbi</title>
    <link>https://www.ayoub-gharbi.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ayoub Gharbi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ayoub-gharbi.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Imagine Cup 2014</title>
      <link>https://www.ayoub-gharbi.org/lifestories/imaginecup2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ayoub-gharbi.org/lifestories/imaginecup2014/</guid>
      <description>Imagine cup was one of the best experiences in my whole life as a student. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t expecting to get the first place in Tunisia since it was the first time I participate in this kind of competitions but our team was strong and we had variety of expertises that facilitated split of tasks and made us work fast and efficiently.
 Imagine Cup Book (© Artist)    0th</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About ME</title>
      <link>https://www.ayoub-gharbi.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ayoub-gharbi.org/about/</guid>
      <description>I’m a 30 years old enthusiastic game programmer from Tunisia. Graduated in 2015 from ESPRIT as a software engineer with a mobile development background. I have been making games since 2012 and I’m currently an independant contractor at TRU LUV working on #SelfCare. I believe that to keep up with the fast-paced technology and innovations popping off every single day, you&amp;rsquo;ve got to love what you are doing.
 I’M A FLEXIBLE PROGRAMMER WITH EAGERNESS TO LEARN I don’t only code because it’s part of my day-to-day job but it’s deeper than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact ME</title>
      <link>https://www.ayoub-gharbi.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ayoub-gharbi.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>Want Contact? Want to talk ? Feel free to reach me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RESUME</title>
      <link>https://www.ayoub-gharbi.org/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ayoub-gharbi.org/resume/</guid>
      <description>KEY QUALIFICATIONS Experienced game programmer with a background in mobile development and around 6 years of experience with aptitude for solving problems.
Highly organized, self-motivated and proficient in guiding product cycles from conception to completion.
Able to stay comfortable with ambiguity and remain calm in the face of the unexpected.
 PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE TRU LUV, CANADA
JAN 2021 - PRESENT
AI &amp;amp; Tools Developer (Contractor/Remotely)
 NUKEDCOCKROACH, TUNISIA
OCT 2016 - DEC 2020</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
